可以给我看漫画吗
Can I see the comics?
这是《纽约时报》
This is the New York Times.
好  能否借我看漫画
Okay, may I see the comics?
伙计们  你们不是要带罗斯去看比赛吗
Guys. I thought you were taking Ross to the game.
是啊  我们约在这里见
We are. He's meeting us here.
不行  瑞秋也跟我们约在这里
No, Rachel's meeting us here!
拜托  他们还是可以共处一室吧
Come on! They can be in the same room.
-你昨晚可是没看到  -现在又怎么了
- You should've been there last night. - Why? What happened now?
罗斯在我们那边
Ross was hanging out at our place.
瑞秋来跟钱德勒借保湿霜
Rachel comes over to borrow some moisturizer from Chandler.
喂  你就不能说借"东西"吗
Hey y-you, how hard is it to say "something"?
瑞秋过来借"东西"
Rachel came over to borrow "something".
反正她和罗斯就开始对骂
Anyway, her and Ross just started yelling at each other.
他怎么敢骂她
Wait. Why was he yelling at her?
跟别人上床的人明明是他
He’s the one who slept with someone else.
我记得他说
Well, I guess he says that
因为当时他们已经分手了
because they were on a break when it happened...
所以她现在就该原谅他了
that she should’ve forgiven him by now.
他真不可理喻  真是的
He is so unreasonable! God!
不过我了解他的意思
Although I think I understand what he means.
天哪  这就好比《60分钟》上的新闻
Oh, my God! This is like 60 Minutes, okay.
一开始你非常生气
when, when, at first you're really mad at
制药公司生产那些药
that pharmaceutical company for making the drug.
后来你又很同情那些人  因为
And then, y'know you just feel bad for the people because...
他们很需要让头发长出来
they needed to make their hair grow.
你们知道这像什么吗
Y'know what this is like?
这像我父母离婚时的情景
This is like when my parents got divorced.
希望童子军活动结束后
Man, I hope Ross doesn't try to kidnap me
罗斯不会企图绑架我
after Cub Scouts.
我做梦梦到罗斯和瑞秋
Y'know I had a dream where Ross and Rachel
仍是一对  从未闹过分手
were still together, they never broke up.
我们在一起玩  大家都很开心
And we were all just like hanging out, and everyone was happy.
我也梦到了
I had the same dream.
也没人跟那个影印店的女孩上过床
Yeah, and nobody slept with the Xerox girl.
我的刚好相反
Oh, I had the opposite dream.
也许会慢慢好起来的
Y'know what maybe it's gonna be okay.
这可都一个星期了
I mean, it's been a week.
是啊  我忘记一段情从不需要
Yeah, I mean it's never taken me more than a week
一星期的时间
to get over a relationship.
你忘情的时间比你洗澡的时间都短
It never takes you more than a shower to get over a relationship.
好了走吧  上路  精彩马上开始
Okay, let's go! Let's hit the road. Let's get the show on it.
好  等我先喝杯咖啡
Okay, let me just get a cup of coffee.
瑞秋  我知道一家超棒的咖啡馆
Oh Rachel, I know the best coffee house
而且超近
and it's sooo close.
比这里还近吗
Closer than here?
你看  我找到一杯咖啡
Oh, hey, look! I found coffee!
我们赶紧走吧
Okay, let's skedaddle.
菲比  我才不喝别人喝剩的咖啡
Pheebs, I'm not just gonna drink somebody's old coffee.
是  公主殿下
Okay, Your Highness.
瑞秋  真的很对不起
"Rachel, I'm really sorry".
没关系  罗斯  你想和好吗
"That's okay, Ross. Wanna get back together?"
好啊好啊
"Yeah, okay".
你们有听到吗
Did anyone else hear that?
-他在吗  -不在
- Is he here? - No.
你的保湿霜
Here's your moisturizer.
你们会爱死我的  听好了
You guys are gonna love me! Okay, check it out.
周四晚上  五张票
Thursday night, five tickets.
卡文·克莱内衣秀
Calvin Klein lingerie show,
你们会跟我一起去
and you guys are coming with me.
我说的时候有发出声音吧
I said that out loud, right?
有  只是我们已经  已经
Yes, yes, it's just that we ah, we kinda all ready...
跟罗斯有约了
made plans with Ross.
这样啊  好吧
Well, okay.
那就这样吧
Well, there you go.
他新买了一套家庭影院组合
No, it's just that he got this new like home theater dealie...
他想  想找我们一起感受一下
and he wants y'know, us to check it out.
是啊  他真的很兴奋
Yeah, he's really excited about it too.
他甚至还在答录机里录了一份节目表
He even recorded showtimes on his answering machine.
-对不起  亲爱的  -没关系
- We're sorry, honey. - Oh, it's okay.
瑞秋  不是我们不想去  真的
Rach, it's, it's ah, it's not that we don't want to, really.
你说的是穿着内衣的模特走秀吗
Are we talking models in their underwear?
还有高跟鞋
And heels.
罗斯先开口约的  所以那晚真的没时间
Ross did ask us first, and we set that night aside.
没关系  是他先约的  很公平
No, hey, come on. If he asked you first, it's only fair.
天哪  我感觉好糟糕
Oh, boy, do I feel bad!
非常糟糕
Very bad.
-钱德勒  你在干什么  -钱德勒
- Chandler, what are you doing? - Chandler!
天哪
Oh, my God!
你又抽烟了
You're smoking again?
那是昨天  我又抽烟了
Well, actually, yesterday, I was smoking again.
今天是"继续抽烟"
Today I'm smoking, still.
嚼了那么多戒烟口香糖
Why would you start again after
你怎么又开始抽了
chewing all that quitting gum?
告诉你们  我父母离婚时跟现在一模一样
Look, I'm telling you this is just like my parents' divorce...
害我开始学会了抽烟
which is when I started smoking in the first place.
你那时不是才9岁吗
Weren't you 9?
是啊
Yeahhh.
我跟你们讲
I'm telling you something,
午睡醒来一支烟  快乐似神仙
that first smoke after naptime....
棒极了  借我吉言  我猜肯定是他
That's great. With my luck, that's gonna be him.
他  是罗斯吗
Him? Him, Ross?
不  是赞美诗253篇《他看顾麻雀》
No, "Hymn" 253: "His Eyes Are on the Sparrow".
我父母闹离婚时
When my parents got divorced,
我便开始用幽默做心理防卫
is when I started using humour as a defence mechanism.
你们周末有计划吗
Hi. Do you guys have plans for the weekend?
我正跟我妹打电话
Because I have my sister on hold,
她说我们可以到她的小屋
and she said that we could have her cabin
过周末  去滑雪
for the weekend and go skiing..
是我先问的吧  我有遵守游戏规则
I'm asking you first, right? I mean I'm playing by the rules.
没问题
Absolutely, yeah!
钱德勒  你又抽烟了  你怎么搞的
Chandler! You're smoking? What are you doing?
闭嘴  你又不是我的亲妈
Shut up! You're not my real mom!
把窗户关上好吗  钱德勒
Hey, can you close that window Chandler?
我的乳头硬到可以割玻璃了
My nipples can cut glass over here!
等下  真的吗
Wait. Really?!
因为我的可以让我免罚单
'Cause mine get me out of tickets.
伙计们  我只想说
Look, you guys I just wanna say,
真的  真的很谢谢你们来陪我
I really, really appreciate you spending this time with me.
这阵子很难熬  真的谢谢你们
It's been a pretty hard time right now, so I just want to say thanks.
谁去抱抱他  我得留在窗子旁边
Can somebody else hug him. I have to stay by the window.
周末要不要来个影碟连播
How about this weekend, we have a laser-disc marathon, okay?
或是来个锦标赛  我有新的
And maybe a tournament on my new...
飞镖盘  怎么样
dart board! What do you think?
连射两天飞镖  一定很好玩
Two days of darts! It'll be great!
不如排在下周末  一定很棒
It'll be great for next weekend.
不  这个周末
No, no, no, this weekend, guys.
不如排在下周末  一定很棒
It'll be great for next weekend.
一定会很好玩
I mean, "It'll be great".
怎么回事
What's going on?
我们被邀请去滑雪
We're sort of invited to go skiing.
要去瑞秋妹妹的小屋
You know, Rachel's sister's cabin?
整个周末吗
So, for the whole weekend?
对不起  是她先约的
We're really sorry, but she did ask us first.
没关系  如果你们要在我失恋的
Yeah, that's okay, I mean if you guys all have to go away...
第一个周末  全都出去玩
for the first weekend I'm alone by myself...
那么我完全可以理解
Y'know then I totally, totally understand.
我可以留下来  我留下来
Y'know what, I can stay. I'm gonna stay.
上次去滑雪
'Cause the last time I went skiing
我根本不敢跳下缆车
I was too afraid to jump off the chair lift.
就这样来来回回地盘旋
I just went round and round.
菲比  我们需要你
Uh, Pheebs we kinda need you to
开你外婆的计程车送我们去
drive everybody all up there in your grandmother's cab.
这样吧  我留下来
But you know what? I'll stay.
不  我留  他是我的哥哥
No, I'll stay. He's my brother.
这是同情吗
What, a "pity stay"?
才不是  我们会玩得很开心
No! We're gonna have fun!
我们来做奶油软糖
We can make fudge.
同情的食物
Pity food?
其实没关系的
Y'know what that's okay, all right.
我不需要你们留下来  谁都不准留下来
I don't need any of you to stay, okay nobody stays.
那我也表示一下好了
Well, then, I might as well offer to stay.
有人在替罗斯难过吗
Does anybody else feel bad about Ross?
你觉得他还在气我们吗
You think he's still mad at us?
在你今早打电话跟他借
He's probably more mad since you
护目镜时  他应该更气了吧
called him this morning to borrow his goggles.
怎么了  我的眼镜不是有色的
What? Mine aren't tinted.
-钱德勒  -怎样
- Chandler. - What?
标示说什么
What does the sign say?
"传送我吧  耶稣"
"Beam me up, Jesus".
是"禁止吸烟"的标示
The "No Smoking" sign.
我外婆的车上不能抽烟
There's no smoking in my grandmother's cab.
那好吧  那我要上厕所
Okay, well, then, I have to go to the bathroom.
拜托
Oh, please!
不行  没事不准停车
No! No unscheduled stops.
到加油站时你再去
You can go when we stop for gas.
看  那边有个休息站
Oh, come on, there's a rest stop right up there.
求你了  我真的得上厕所
Come on, I really have to go!
现在我也想上了
Oh, now I have to go!
到了
Here we go.
-坐好了  -什么
- Okay, brace yourselves! - What?
好吧
Okay.
-你不去吗  -不了
- Aren't you gonna go? - No, Thank you.
算了  瑞秋从不上公共厕所的
No, Rachel never pees in public restrooms.
那里面都没有卫生纸的好吧
Well, they never have any paper in there y'know.
所以我的原则是"没手纸  不嘘嘘"
So my rule is, "No tissue, no tushy".
既然大家都下车了
Well, if everybody's going....
别  不要关门  因为
No, y'know what don't close it! 'Cause the...
钥匙  在里面
keys.. are in there!
不要啊不要啊
Oh, no-no-no-no-no-no.
-怎么了  -我打火机在里面呢
- What's going on? - My lighter's in there!
该死  排气管不够烫  点不着
Damn! The tailpipe's not hot enough to light this.
别着急
Relax okay.
我会开门  谁有衣架
I can get this open. Anybody got a coat hanger?
我有
Oh, I do.
不对  等一下
Op, no, wait a minute,
今天早上穿衣服时拿掉了
I took it out of my shirt when I put it on this morning.
要是你的父母没有离婚
So, if your parents hadn't got divorced...
你就能像正常人一样回答问题吗
you'd be able to answer a question like a normal person?
我需要铁丝类的东西把它撬开
Look, I just need a wire something to jimmy it.
谁能把胸罩的钢圈给我
Oh hey, one of you guys give me the underwire from your bra.
-什么  -什么呀
- What? - What?
快  谁的胸部最大
Come on! Who has the biggest boobs?
拜托
Please!
谁的胸部最大
Whoever has the biggest boobs,
胸罩也就最大  那么钢圈也最大
has the biggest bra therefore has the biggest wire.
-不要  我不要脱  -很贵耶
- No, not getting my bra! - It's too expensive!
要想回车里  就得有钢圈
If you wanna get back in the car, we need the wire.
你们决定
Your call.
好吧  莫妮卡的最大
Okay, Monica's are the biggest.
这两个飞机场吗
These tiny little non-breasts?
拜托  绝对是瑞秋
Please! It's gotta be Rachel.
什么  哪有  我那是骗人的
What, no, no, no, mine are deceptively small.
我有时候还会往里面垫东西呢
I mean, I actually sometimes stuff my bra.
所以你的胸罩还是很大
Well, then, your bra would still be big.
我都垫在胸罩外面
No, I stuff outside the bra.
小姐们  别争了好吗
Ladies, let's just compromise, okay?
菲比  瑞秋  脱了莫妮卡的胸罩
Phoebe, Rachel, take off Monica's bra.
好啦  算了
All right, forget it, never mind.
-用我的吧  -谢谢
- You can have mine. - Thank you.
钱德勒  你干什么  那里就有垃圾桶
Chandler, what are you doing? There's a trash can right there.
我想如果乱丢垃圾能引来"哭泣的印第安人"
I thought if I littered, that crying Indian might
我们就有救了
come by and save us.
好了  拿去
Okay. There.
菲比  谢了  你真大方
Thank you, Phoebe. That's very, very generous.
好  现在来比谁的屁股翘
Okay, now let's decide who has the nicest ass.
上车吧
And there you go!
钱德勒
Chandler!
至少让我爽一下
Well, at least let me smoke it to the good part!
不要吧
Oh, no!
-怎么  怎么了  -怎么了
- What, what's it, what's going on? - What?
我碰过这种状况
Yeah, this has happened before.
-那你会修吗  -会  加上油就好
- So you know how to fix it? - Yep. Put more gas in.
你怎么来了
Hi. What are you doing here?
我只是在想  我们分手时
Well, oh just ah, I was just wondering, when you and I split up...
你有没有拿到一卷带子
did you get the tape that was
录了《野战医院》最后一集
half the last episode of M.A.S.H...
和人质回国的新闻
and half the hostages coming home?
有  但现在是苏珊和我游墨西哥
Ah yeah, but now it's Susan and me in Mexico
和人质回国的新闻
and the hostages coming home.
-本呢  -在睡觉
- Where's Ben? - He's sleeping.
我来得不是时候吗
Ooh, is this a ah, is this a bad time?
没错  苏珊马上就要回来了
Yeah, actually. Susan's gonna be here any minute.
今天是个纪念日
It's kind of an anniversary.
你们不是一月结的婚吗
I thought you guys got married in uh, January.
是另一个纪念日
A different kind of anniversary.
总之
So anyway...
蜡烛  香槟
Candles, champagne....
纪念日真好
Yeah, anniversaries are great...
因为爱是永恒的
'Cause you know love lasts forever.
什么也比不上爱情可靠  妥妥的
There's nothing like it in this life. Money in the bank.
瑞秋和我分手了
So Rachel and I broke up.
-天哪  罗斯  真可惜  -是啊
- God, Ross, I am so sorry! - Yeah, well.
你知道吗
You know what?
我很想陪你聊一聊
I wanna talk to you about this so much...
但要找个能长谈的时间
but we should probably do it when we can really get into it.
-明天晚餐可以吗  -太好了
- You free for dinner tomorrow? - I'd love that.
我也是
Me too.
一切都是因为瑞秋找到新工作
I guess it all started when Rachel got this new job.
好的  汽车协会可以来接我们
Okay, yeah. Triple A can pick us up.
我们靠近哪个镇
What town are we near?
佛利蒙特
Fremont.
威斯蒙特
Westmont.
威斯柏格
Westberg?
不知道就别说
Then why are you answering?
知道我们在哪条路上吗
Do you know at least what route we're on?
绝对是27号公路
Yeah, we are definitely on Route 27.
好  我们在27号公路的一个休息站
Okay. We are at a rest stop on Route 27.
好的  没有27号公路
Okay. There is no Route 27.
-不是93号就是76号  -我不知道
- Okay, either 93 or 76. - I don't know.
对不起
I'm sorry,
我每次来都在后座睡觉
I always slept in the back when we drove up here.
能不能请人沿着76号公路
Okay. Can you just send someone up and down 76
将所有休息站都挨个找找
and check every rest stop?
还有93号公路
And also 93?
好的
Okay.
好吧  他们不干
Yeah, no they don't do that.
好吧  一定会有人来救我们
Okay. Somebody will come and save us.
谁  这一个半小时
Who? I mean have you seen a car
有车子经过吗
come by here in the last hour and a half?
我觉得应该找罗斯
I think we should call Ross,
他可以开车来载我们
maybe he can get a car and come pick us up.
不要  我不要跟罗斯同车
No! No, I am not getting in a car with Ross!
我们必须
we will just have to...
在这里耗着
live here!
-但是好冷  -不行
- But it's so cold. - No you guys!
我不跟他同车
I am not getting in a car with him,
大家再想别的办法
you'll have to think of something else.
太好了  乔伊和钱德勒回来了
Oh good, Joey and Chandler are back!
求援过程还顺利吗
So the "going for help" went well?
是  去高速公路时老烟枪半路上就挂了
Oh yeah, Smokey Joe here got halfway to the highway and collapsed.
我的肺活量跟两岁小孩一样
I have the lung capacity of a 2-year-old.
那你为什么要抽烟
Then why are you smoking?
我很不安
It's very unsettling.
对吧  真是太过分了
Right? I mean, it's pretty unbelievable.
他们就这样走了  连头也没回一下
I mean they just took off, took off without even looking back.
我才不需要他们呢
Y'know I don't, I don't need them.
我有你们这些朋友
I've got you guys now as friends.
你和苏珊
You and Susan.
苏珊会很高兴的
Susan will be so pleased.
717是哪里
Where's 717?
你有帮苏珊留一些菜对吧
You have more of these for Susan, right?
没有  不过没关系
No, but that's okay.
还有酸黄瓜可以吃
I'll just put out pickles or something.
-罗斯  谢天谢地  -菲比
- Ross, thank God! - Pheebs?
为什么这么小声
Why are you whispering?
我吃了一只虫子
I ate a bug.
瑞秋  这里的卫生棉条只要一分钱
Hey, Rach! The tampons here are only a penny.
我们买来囤货吧
Let's stock up.
罗斯  我们的车没油了
Listen Ross, we ran of gas and
又不知道方位  所以没办法叫拖车
we don't know where we are so we can't get a tow truck.
现在需要帮忙了
Now you want a favor?
对  拜托
Yes, please.
很抱歉你们的车子挂了  菲比
Well, oh, I'm sorry your car broke down, Pheebs...
但是我忙着跟
but I'm a little too busy with
我真正的朋友联络感情
some of my real friends right now.
不过等你们安全到家  记得通知我好吗
But please call to let me know you got home safely okay?
菲比  等一下
Phoebe, hang on a second.
拿着  开我的车去接你朋友
Here, take my car, go pick up your friends.
不要  我才不要去接他们
No, I'm not gonna pick them up.
听着  我们都知道你会去的
Listen, we both know you're gonna do it,
因为你不是混蛋
because you're not a jerk.
要么你再骂个半小时
So you can either sulk here for a half hour
然后去接他们
and then go pick them up...
要么节省时间去车上骂
or save us both time and sulk in the car.
瑞秋不想让我
Rachel doesn't want me...
很遗憾瑞秋移情别恋
Look, I-I-I am sorry that Rachel dumped you
为了那个马克把你甩了
'Cause she fell in love with that Mark guy...
你是无辜的受害者
and you're the innocent victim in this.
但不要为了瑞秋迁怒你的朋友
But don't punish your friends for what Rachel did to you.
你说得对
Yeah, you're right.
菲比  等一下  罗斯要跟你说
Phoebe, hang on a second. Ross wants to say something.
什么
What?
你跟别人上床了
You slept with someone else?
我们当时分手了  好吗
We were on a break! OK?
我们  我们
We were, we were...
对  你们在哪里
Yeah, Where are you?
我去找你们
I'll find you.
你跟别的女人上床了
You slept with another woman?
你还敢说
Oh, you're one to talk.
好了
Okay, done!
什么是"命救"
What's "pleh"?
就是"救命"反过来
That's "help" spelled backwards...
好让直升机上的人看得懂
so that the helicopters can read it from the air.
"呆子"反过来怎么写
What's "dufus" spelled backwards?
有车
Car! Car!
罗斯出来兜风了
Oh, it's Ross on one of his drives!
他来干什么
What is he doing here?
他来救你们一命
He is saving your butt.
除非我惹到了某个人
Unless of course I'm stepping on some toes here...
那我可以闪人
in which case I could just mosey on.
州际公路上有很多人需要帮助
I have got plenty of people to help on the interstate.
别这样
Come on!
-我们需要你帮助  -好吧  好吧
- We need your help, please! -Fine, fine.
完了  这下谁都看不懂了
Oh, no! Now it's not gonna make any sense.
各位
You guys...
罗斯怎么办  他大老远跑来
what do we do about Ross? He drove all the way up here.
难道要叫他回去  我们自己去滑雪
What do we do? Just send him back, then we'll go skiing?
烦死了  烦死了
This is horrible. It's just horrible.
你们觉得要不要叫上罗斯一起去
Guys, do you think we should ask Ross to come along?
那瑞秋呢  要怎么向她开口
I know, what about Rachel? How are we gonna even ask her?
开什么口
Ask me what?
可不可以请罗斯一起去滑雪
If it might be okay if Ross came skiing?
不是我们要问的
No, I wasn't gonna ask that.
你们太扯了  不行  他不能去
You guys are unbelievable. No, he cannot come!
-什么  -烦死了
- Excuse me? - It's horrible!
求求你  让我去你那独一无二
Oh, please? Can't I come to
神奇无比的小屋吧
your special, magical cabin?
罗斯  你去干什么  你滑雪那么烂
Why would you even want to come Ross? You're a horrible skier.
真是说到我的痛处啊  我滑雪烂啊
Hitting me where it hurts! My ski skills!
又来了
Here we go again.
我没办法应付了
I can't handle this, you guys.
我能啊  "应付"就是我的中间名
I can handle it. "Handle" is my middle name.
其实是我的名字(Chandler)去头去尾
Actually, it's the middle part of my first name.
菲比  你的车子好了
All right, Pheebs, your cab's ready.
好了  走吧
All right, let's go.
不客气
You're welcome.
抱歉  你在跟我说话  还是在跟别人上床
I'm sorry. Were you speaking to me, or sleeping with someone else?
我们当时分手了
We were on a break!
好吧  罗斯  你干脆在答录机里
OK. Y'know Ross why don't you just
把这句话录下来得了
put that on your answering machine?
本来就是  不止我一个人这么想
It's valid, and I'm not the only one who thinks so.
莫妮卡也同意
Monica agrees with me.
什么
What?
我不知道
I don't know.
你昨晚就是这么说的
That's what you said last night.
我是说我能理解
What I said was that I understood.
乔伊才是认同你的那个人
Joey is the one who agreed with you.
-很好  -是吗  乔伊
- Okay. - Really, Joey?
什么
What?
我觉得  这件事没有什么对错之分
You know what? There is no right or wrong here.
不  我觉得错的是谁其实非常明显
No, I think it's very obvious who's wrong here.
乔伊显然不这么想
Obviously not to Joey.
什么
What?
乔伊和莫妮卡跟我感觉是一样的
Joey and Monica feel the way I do!
你只会装无辜
You and this innocent puppy act!
你们猜我在学谁
Hey, guess who I am?
看你们把钱德勒害得多惨
Look what you're doing to Chandler!
听着  我们知道你们都很难受  好吗
Look. We know that this is really, really hard for you guys. Okay?
你们可以不爱对方
You don't...You don't have to love each other. Okay?
你们现在甚至不必喜欢对方
You don't even have to like each other much right now.
但是拜托你们必须得设法和平相处
But please, you have to figure out a way to be around each other.
别让我们左右为难
And not put us in the middle.
对  不然的话  我们只能
Yeah, otherwise, I mean that's, that's,
我们以后就不用在一起了
that's just it for us hanging out together.
明白吗  你们真的想这样吗
You know? Is that what you want?
讲理一点好吗
Can you be civil?
-好  -可以啊
- Yeah. - I can.
很好  回车上吧  冷死了
Good, all right, let's get back in the car. It's freezing...
我的咪咪没有支撑好空荡
and my chest is unsupported.
等一下
Wait a second!
现在是怎样  谁要跟谁走
I mean, what are we doing? Who's going with who?
你们去吧
Look, you guys should...you guys should go.
你们都计划好了
You know, you planned this all out...
我不想破坏  所以你们去吧
and I don't wanna ruin it. So you guys should just go.
可是  你大老远开车来
Come on, man. You drove all the way up here.
没事  不用  反正我还得去还车
No, no, really, I've got to take the car back anyway.
我明天一整天都要陪本玩
I'm spending all day tomorrow with Ben.
没关系  你们去吧
It's fine, okay? Just go.
不要有罪恶感  真的
No guilt, I promise.
谢谢
Thank you.
回去再打电话给你
All right, we'll call you when we get back.
-好的  -我们可以去看电影
- Okay. - Maybe we can, like, go to a movie or something.
-好  -或是去看马术表演
- Okay. - Okay. Or the rodeo!
-听起来不错  -好
- That would be great. -Okay.
我刚才模仿的是《海神号历险记》里的
I was being Shelley Winters from
雪莉·温特斯
The Poseidon Adventure.
我知道
I know.
再见
Bye!
-罗斯  -抱歉  我来晚了
- Ross. - Hi. Sorry I'm late.
-你在睡觉吗  -没
- Were you sleeping? - No.
那就好
Oh, great.
我给车子换了新电池
Listen, oh I had to get you a whole new battery.
我换了个最好的
I got the best I could.
因为这种钱不能省
'Cause that's not where you want to skimp.
你真聪明  罗斯
You're a genius, Ross.
花了112元
It came to about $112.
管他呢  算110块就好
But what the hell, just call it an even 110?
明天给你  再见
I'll pay you tomorrow okay. Bye!
他们都走了
So they all took off.
看他们离开蛮难受的
It was pretty hard watching them go, you know?
好  再见
Yeah, okay. Bye.
那我走啦
So I'm gonna take off then.